[{"question": " chandler.", "answer": " ms. tedlock. you're looking lovely today. and may i say, that is a very flattering sleeve length on you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " yeah. well, mr. kostelick wants you to stop by his office at the end of the day.", "answer": " oh, listen. if this is about those prank memos, i had nothing to do with them. really. nothing at all. really.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " never mind. but it was going to be really good.", "answer": " what's going on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " what is it?", "answer": " so, it's a typical day at work. i'm putting in my numbers, and then big al calls me into his office and tells me he wants to make me processing supervisor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " that's great!", "answer": " so.... i quit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " why? this was supposed to be a temp job!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " uh, chandler... you've been there for five years.", "answer": " if i took this promotion, it'd be like admitting that this is what i actually do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " so was it a lot more money?", "answer": " it doesn't matter. i just don't want to be one of those guys that's in his office until twelve o'clock at night worrying about the wenus.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " ... the wenus?", "answer": " weekly estimated net usage systems. a processing term. rach:  oh. that wenus.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " so what're you going to do?", "answer": " i don't know. that's the thing. i don't know what i want to do. i just know i'm not going to figure it out working there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oooh! i have something you can do! i have this new massage client... steve?  anyway, he's opening up a restaurant and he's looking for a head chef.", "answer": " um... hi there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " hi!  oh, yeah, no, i know. you're a chef. i know, and i thought of you first, but um, chandler's the one who needs a job right now, so....", "answer": " yeah... i just don't have that much cheffing experience. unless it's an all-toast restaurant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " yeah, yeah! well, what kind of food is he looking for?", "answer": " well, he wants to do some ecclectic, so he's looking for someone who can, you know, create the entire menu.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  oh my god!", "answer": " yeah, i know!  well, what do you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " thanks, phoeb. but i just don't see myself in a big white hat.", "answer": " ok.  hey monica! guess what!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " can you see my nipples through this shirt?", "answer": " no. but don't worry, i'm sure they're still there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " where are you going, mr. suity-man?", "answer": " well, i have an appointment to see dr. robert pillman, career counselor a-gogo.  i added the \"a-gogo\".", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " work counselor?", "answer": " hey, you guys all know what you want to do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " i don't!", "answer": " hey, you guys in the living room all know what you want to do. you know, you have goals. you have dreams. i don't have a dream.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " oh, i love my life, i love my life!", "answer": " ooh! brian's song!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " the meeting with the guy went great?", "answer": " so great! he showed me where the restaurant's going to be. it's this cute little place on 10th street. not too big, not too small. just right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " was it formerly owned by a blonde woman and some bears?", "answer": " so anyway, i'm cooking dinner for him monday night. you know, kind of like an audition. and phoebe, he really wants you to be here, which will be great for me because you can 'ooh' and 'ahh' and make yummy noises.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " what are you going to make?", "answer": "  yummy noises.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": "  and monica, what are you going to make?", "answer": " i don't know. i don't know. it's just going to be so great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " hey guys, does anybody know a good date place in the neighborhood?", "answer": " how about tony's? if you can finish a 32-ounce steak, it's free.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " ok, ahem, hey, does anybody know a good place if you're not dating a puma?", "answer": " who are you going out with?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " oh, is this the bug lady?", "answer": "  bzzzz.... i love you, ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " her name is celia. she's not a bug lady. she's curator of insects at the museum.", "answer": " so what are you guys going to do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " oh, i just thought we could go out to dinner, and then maybe bring her back to my place and i might introduce her to my monkey.", "answer": " and he's not speaking metaphorically.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": "  so.... back to your place...you thinking, maybe...  huh-huh?", "answer": " well, i don't know....  huh-huh.... but i'm hoping  huh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " he's not going to hurt you! keep going, celia. marcel...", "answer": " i can't stand this! he's got his claws in my...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  ok, try this salmon mousse.", "answer": "  mmmm. good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " is it better than the other salmon mousse?", "answer": " it's creamier.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " yeah, well, is that better?", "answer": " i don't know. we're talking about whipped fish, monica. i'm just happy i'm keeping it down, y'know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " my god! what happened to you?", "answer": " eight and a half hours of aptitude tests, intelligence tests, personality tests... and what do i learn?  \"you are ideally suited for a career in data processing for a large multinational corporation.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " that's so great! 'cause you already know how to do that!", "answer": " can you believe it? i mean, don't i seem like somebody who should be doing something really cool? you know, i just always pictured myself doing... something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": "  oh chandler, i know, i know... oh, hey! you can see your nipples through this shirt!", "answer": "  hey, maybe this'll cheer you up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " ooh, you know, i had a grape about five hours ago, so i'd better split this with you.", "answer": " it's supposed to be that small. it's a pre-appetizer. the french call it an amouz-bouche.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " ten dollars an hour for what?", "answer": " oh, i asked one of the waitresses at work if she'd help me out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": "  waitressing?", "answer": " uh-oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " well... of course i thought of you! but... but...", "answer": " but, but?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " but, you see, it's just... this night has to go just perfect, you know? and, well, wendy's more of a... professional waitress.", "answer": " oh! i see. and i've sort of been maintaining my amateur status so that i can waitress in the olympics.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " talk to me.", "answer": " ok.... um, a weird thing happened to me on the train this morning...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " no no no. talk... dirty.", "answer": "  wha... what, here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " yes...", "answer": " ah....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " say something..... hot.", "answer": "  er.... um.....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " um... uh.... vulva. commercial", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  vulva?", "answer": " alright, i panicked, alright? she took me by surprise. you know, but it wasn't a total loss. i mean, we ended up cuddling.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": "  whoaa!! you cuddled? how many times??", "answer": " shut up! it was nice. i just... i don't think i'm the dirty-talking kind of guy, you know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " what's the big deal? you just say what you want to do to her. or what you want her to do to you. or what you think other people might be doing to each other. i'll tell you what. just try something on me.", "answer": "  please be kidding.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " why not? come on! close your eyes and tell me what you'd like to be doing right now.", "answer": " ok.  i'm in my apartment...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " ....yeah... what else?", "answer": " that's it. i'm in my apartment, you're not there, we're not having this conversation.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": "  alright, look, i'll start, ok?", "answer": " joey, please.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " come on. come on. alright, ready, look!  oh... ross.... you get me so hot. i want your lips on me now.", "answer": "  wow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " alright, now you say something.", "answer": " i... ahem... i really don't think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " come on! you like this woman, right?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " you want to see her again, right?", "answer": " sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " well if you can't talk dirty to me, how're you going to talk dirty to her? now tell me you want to caress my butt!", "answer": " ok, turn around.  i just don't want you staring at me when i'm doing this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": "  alright, alright. i'm around. go ahead.", "answer": " ahem... i want.... ok, i want to... feel your... hot, soft skin with my lips.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " there you go! keep going. keep going!", "answer": " i, er...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " ....and....", "answer": " say it... say it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " ....with??", "answer": "  funny story!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " it's ok. it's ok. i was always rooting for you two kids to get together.", "answer": " hey chandler, while you were sleeping that guy from your old job called again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " again?", "answer": " and again, and again, and again...  hello?  and again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " well?", "answer": "  wow! it's huge! it's so much bigger than the cubicle. oh, this is a cube.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh! you have a window!", "answer": " yes indeedy!  with a beautiful view of...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " oh look! that guy's peeing!", "answer": "  ok, that's enough of the view. check this out, look at this. sit down, sit down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": "  ok.", "answer": " this is great!  helen, could you come in here for a moment?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " who was that?", "answer": " wendy bailed. i have no waitress.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " ten dollars an hour.", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " twelve dollars an hour.", "answer": " mon. i wish i could, but i've made plans to walk around.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " you know, rachel, when you ran out of your wedding, i was there for you. i put a roof over your head, and if that means nothing to you...  twenty dollars an hour.", "answer": " done.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " well hello! welcome to monica's. may i take your coat?", "answer": " hi steve!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " hello, monica.  hello, greeter girl.", "answer": "  this is rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": "  yeah, ok.", "answer": "  mmmmmm! everything smells so delicious! you know, i can't remember a time i smelt such a delicious combination of  of, ok, smells.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " it's a lovely apartment.", "answer": " oh, thank you. would you like a tour?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " what's up?", "answer": "  in the cab, on the way over, steve blazed up a doobie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " smoked a joint? you know, lit a bone? weed? hemp? ganja?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " ok, ok. i'm with you, cheech. ok.", "answer": "  is it dry in here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " no. let me get you some wine!", "answer": " yeah, i think we're ready for our first course.  ok, um, these are rot-shrimp ravioli, and celantro pondou sauce... ... with just a touch of mints... and... ... ginger.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " well, slap my ass and call me judy! these are fantastic!", "answer": " i'm so glad you liked them!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " like 'em? i could eat a hundred of them!", "answer": " oh, well... um, that's all there are of those. but in about eight and a half minutes, we'll be serving some delicious onion tartlets.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " excuse me? can i help you with anything?", "answer": " you know, i don't know what i'm looking for.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": "  ah, cool! taco shells! you know, these are... they're like a little corn envelope.", "answer": "  you know that? you don't want to spoil your appetite.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " you know, if you just wait another... six and a half minutes...", "answer": " macaroni and cheese! we gotta make this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " why don't you just have a seat here?  ok... give me the gummi-bears.", "answer": "  no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " give them to me.", "answer": " alright, we'll share.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " no, give me the...", "answer": " well then you can't have any.  man overboard! i think he's drowning.  hey fellows! grab on a sugar-o... save yourself!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": "  that's it! dinner is over!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " what a tool!", "answer": " you don't want to work for a guy like that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " i know... it's just... i thought this was, you know... it.", "answer": " look, you'll get there. you're an amazing chef.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " yeah! you know all those yummy noises? i wasn't faking.", "answer": "  so, er... how did it go with celia?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " oh, i was unbelievable.", "answer": " all right, ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " i was the james michener of dirty talk. it was the most elaborate filth you have ever heard. i mean, there were different characters, plot lines, themes, a motif... at one point there were villagers.", "answer": " whoa! and the...  huh-huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " well, ahem... you know, by the time we'd finished with all the dirty talk, it was kinda late... and we were both kind of exhausted, so...", "answer": " you cuddled.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " yeah, which was nice.", "answer": " you guys wanna try and catch a late movie or something?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " maybe, but shouldn't we wait for chandler?", "answer": " yeah, where the hell is he?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " eeeee!", "answer": " how about over here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " aaaaah!", "answer": " see, that just means it's working. does this hurt?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " what about this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}]